Our worst fear has been realized.
Hey, stop that!
Your clothes are falling off.
I think we'll need diapers and...
milk.
Breast feeding?!
A pure young maiden can't produce breast milk, you idiots!
Diapers, a bottle, powdered milk...
We might need hot water, too.
That's a good girl.
I never thought I'd ever hold Iori like this.
Nothing's happening to Taichi, and Balloon Vine still hasn't appeared.
This all seems pretty irregular.
Y-Yeah...
Onee!
Anzu?
And Mihashi-san?
What are you doing here?
Who are they?
Kiriyama's little sister and someone from her karate days.
I talked to Mihashi-san about how strange you've been acting lately, and we decided to follow you.
Whose baby is that?
Well...
You hold them off.
Come on, let's go!
Hey!
Wait right there!
You're not going anywhere.
First of all, what's with that baby?
What do you mean?
No way...
You had a baby with that guy?
No, you're wrong.
That'll never happen!
Then the girl who was holding her was the mother?
No!
Huh?
But if you're the father...
Stop assuming that.
Then how else can you explain this love triangle?
It's not a love triangle!
I got Anzu to go home.
Coming up with an excuse is going to be a pain.
Hey, Kiriyama.
What club were you in again?
Huh? The Cultural Research Club.
What do you do there?
Um...
We get together in the club room and talk or play around...
What's the point of that?
The point? Nothing really...
Is there anything you're trying to accomplish?
Is there anything you're living for?
Seriously...
Living for? I'm not...
So you're just goofing off?
Quit it!
What?
Who are you to judge me?!
What happened to the cool, serious Kiriyama Yui?
What about the old me?
I'm saying that you're nothing compared to the old you!
Was everything you said a lie?
What about our promise?
I told you...
I don't remember making any promise!
I'll open your eyes for you.
Fight me!
Mihashi-san, have you ever won against me?
Wait, are you serious?
Kiriyama!
So what happened?
Kiriyama lost.
We got the girl to go home after telling her we'd explain everything later.
Hey, stop, Iori!
Don't get too far from me!
Cheer up, Nana's sister!
Oh, right!
Let's play with Nana later!
She said she got a fun new game—
Shut up!
I'm Kiriyama Yui!
Oh...
I'm... sorry...
No, I mean...
I'm sorry.
Sorry.
Why do I keep thinking that she's Nana's sister?!
I'm in love with Yui now.
But is that just because Yui looks just like Nana?
Don't let it get to you.
And so, the new year came.
We ended up spending New Year's Eve and New Year's Day together.
We're spending January 2nd together, too, huh?
So it's these two today?
No!
What's wrong, Yui?!
What's wrong?
What's wrong, Yui?
Are you okay?
M-Men...
I...
Okay. I know.
It's all right.
Just calm down. Take a deep breath.
Looks like her time regressed to right after she was assaulted.
It must have been horrible.
She couldn't have gone to school like that.
I'm going out for some air.
Hey, quit shaking.
You're distracting me.
Sorry.
Aren't you going to do something?
You're wasting time just spacing out.
Then can I read that book?
Wow, Inaban was harsh back then, too.
She's not a bad kid, but she's got a sharp tongue.
But you won't hate Inaban for it, will you?
Of course not.
That's good.
You've been out of the house every day since New Year's.
Has your mom asked you anything about it?
Huh?
No, right now...
Well, yeah.
Oh, I got my time regressed today?
How old was I?
14.
Kiriyama was 14, too.
Yui!
Are you all right, Yui?
I remembered...
everything.
And...
I...
Yui, it's all right.
It's all right now.
You sure you can make it home by yourself?
Yeah. I'm okay now.
Sorry to make you all worry about me.
Mihashi-san...
Kiriyama, can you explain yourself now?
I don't understand. It just doesn't feel right.
I don't think it's any of your business.
Don't treat me like that!
I just wanted—
Shut up!
I quit karate. The end.
But our promise...
I don't care about some dumb promise!
I don't want to remember about the past.
Hey...
I don't know what's going on,
but Yui, would it hurt to hear her out?
What? You have no right to tell me what to do.
But you should at least listen to—
A half-hearted guy like you has no right to tell me what to do!
Half-hearted?
You're just a half-hearted guy who says he loves me because I look like an old girlfriend of his!
Get it right!
I'm doing everything I can right!
You're the one not doing it right!
What's that supposed to mean?
You aren't confronting any of your problems.
You aren't now, and you never have!
But I...
You're the one giving up and making excuses!
Sorry it has to be me again.
I remembered.
Huh?
My promise.
Before she moved away, Mihashi-san came up to me after a tournament.
She said that the next time we'd fight was at nationals.
But I completely forgot.
I gave up and lived half-heartedly.
I'm like some side character, aren't I?
Some side character?
Hey, Taichi...
I love you, Taichi.
Huh?!
Wait a second!
Seriously, wait a second!
This is going to cause me a whole heap of trouble!
Let's say someone kept saying that they loved you like that.
If you never gave them a real response, would their feelings change?
I don't know.
I've never been in that position.
Has anyone ever confessed to you, and you just let it sit?
If the person who kept confessing just stopped,
what should the other person do?
Isn't that for the other person to decide?
You think so, too?
I think I used to be strong.
Not just strong in karate.
I didn't need to rely on others.
But now...
I depend on everyone around me.
And I can't do anything to return the favor.
I gave up on my dreams and left it all behind me.
My life is so pointless and empty.
I'm completely worthless now.
But I can't help it.
I'm no one important.
Thanks for coming out here for me.
Was this Nagase's idea?
Yeah.
We need to do something.
But I don't think Yui should be here for this.
Aoki, do you not love Yui anymore?
No, I still do, but my memories are all jumbled.
It feels like I'm forgetting something important.
Something important?
Yeah. It's just at the tip of my tongue.
I don't want to stick my nose in other people's love lives.
I messed up last time, after all.
So this is all I'll say:
You're thinking too hard.
"Thinking too hard"?
I can't believe that Inaban, who always bashed Aoki for being illogical, would tell him not to think!
I can change, too, you know.
I know the power of love now.
H-Hey! Saying it like that isn't fair!
You're the one who isn't being fair!
With that we're-connected-on-a-deeper-level look on your face!
When did I make a face like that?!
What kind of face should I be making?
I remember now!
I...
forgot to be laid-back!
Huh?
Yeah.
Back then, I decided...
Back when?
I'm going to go see Nana.
We're counting on you if anything happens.
As far as we know, you're never going to get your time regressed.
Y-Yeah.
Got it.
Aoki, why do you want to see Nishino-san?
To see if my love is true.
What just happened?!
Why does Aoki suddenly look kind of cool?
Even if it means quitting the CRC, I'm going to be me, right to the bitter end.
That's my philosophy.
Back in middle school...
Huh?
A girl in my class died in a car accident.
We were kind of close, so it was a real shock.
It made me think, you never know when someone's going to die.
She went to cram school and worked really hard.
But she died, so it was all for nothing.
I'm not saying that all her efforts were pointless.
But that's why I decided to enjoy life to the fullest.
That way, I can consider my life awesome no matter when I die.
That's your philosophy?
Right.
I don't know if it's right or wrong.
But I'll need to live it to the fullest to know.
Holy crap, it's freezing!
Let's hurry then.
Do you know the address?
Yeah, I brought her New Year's card with me.
Is this the right street?
It should be around here.
Yoshifumi?!
Nana...
Yoshifumi, why are you...
Sorry, I just had to see you.
Huh?
Nana...
Yes?
I loved you so much.
But now, there's someone I love even more.
I see.
Sorry.
I came all this way just to tell you that.
That's okay. Thanks for coming to see me.
So... who's he?
Don't tell me he's the person you're in love with.
Not a chance in hell!
I see.
That's good.
Are you doing anything now?
You came all the way here. Want to come in for a while?
No, that's okay.
We need to take the overnight bus home.
Huh?
I see.
I guess that's it, then.
Oh, and my hair...
I cut it at the end of last year.
I see.
All right! It's about time we left.
Yeah.
Let's get going, Taichi!
Already?
See you.
Good-bye.
Wait, Aoki!
Why are we running?
We have plenty of time before noon!
I need to tell her now! There isn't a moment to lose!
Taichi!
Whad'ja get me?
Nothing?
What'd you say?! You didn't get me anything?!
I told you to text him.
Yui.
Living in the moment as it comes is really important to me.
And I don't think very hard about anything.
So when I remembered how I felt in the past, I was really confused.
I went to see her and to see if my love is true.
And now I know.
I really loved Nana.
I can't act like I didn't
because I was living life to the fullest.
I see.
But I'm living life to the fullest even harder now.
So I can't ignore what I feel now either.
I was in love with Nishino Nana.
And now, I'm in love with Kiriyama Yui.
What's wrong with that?
But that's because I look like Nishino-san.
That's not it at all.
Nana is Nana.
You are you.
It's not about what you look like.
I fell in love with you for who you are.
Am I really worth it?
Of course!
You're worth more than anything in the world!
At the very least, you are to me right now.
Because I love you, Yui.
That's all I wanted to say.
I hate myself! I hate myself! I hate myself!
I hate myself!
I knew all along!
I knew, but everyone was so nice to me.
I was just waiting for someone to...
Yui?
I'm afraid of men!
I could've just explained myself, and that'd be the end of it!
Is it that I didn't want to remember?
Or did I think I was stupid for trying so hard?
I don't know, either!
But I was making excuses!
I gave up on everything!
In the end, I couldn't even take the first step!
I used to hate losing.
When did I stop caring if I won or lost?
My worth is something I have to earn.
If I don't want to be a side character,
I just need to become a main character.
Thanks to you, I want to be strong again.
Thanks.
Yui, you don't need to force yourself to—
Don't stop her, Iori.
I won.
See?
All I had to do was try.
A-Are you all right?
I won't lose.
I won't lose ever again.
What's this feeling?
I haven't felt like this in forever.
The phrase, "In Heaven and on Earth, I alone am honored," is mine.
It's got my name all over it.
Yui...
You might think that phrase means "I'm the best in the world,"
but it doesn't.
A-Anyway—
Yoshifumi-kun, how old are you?
I'm 10.
Okay.
Listen, I might not be able to right now,
but one day, I'll make sure you know that I'm Kiriyama Yui.
The one and only, who no one will mistake for someone else!
Huh?
Of course you're Kiriyama-san.
You do kinda look like Nana, though.
Come here. I'll get you some clothes.
Okay.
How does he know who she is now?
Because everything's sorted out in his head?
Who cares why?
It looks like everything worked out.
It's between the two of them, now.
But seriously, how long is this going to go on for?
If school starts while this is happening...
Don't worry.
It shouldn't go on for that long.
How do you know that?
Huh?
Taichi, you're hiding something from us, aren't you?
N-No, I'm...
What's wrong, Inaban?
I thought that you not getting your time regressed was fishy.
What do you know?
What are you hiding from us?
No, it's not!
Mom!
Open the door!
It's me!
Choosing you was a mistake.
Stop right there, you idiot!
Would you do anything differently?
There's no way to...
I...